<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FRAMEWORK on dipbits Technology Ltd</title>
    <link>https://dipbitstech.com/tags/framework/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FRAMEWORK on dipbits Technology Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:33:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dipbitstech.com/tags/framework/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Impletment User Auth Username or Email in Laravel</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2023/05/04/laravel_auth_with_username_email/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:33:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2023/05/04/laravel_auth_with_username_email/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Laravel is a popular PHP framework that is widely used for web application development. One of the most important features of any web application is authentication. In this blog, we will look at how to perform authentication with email or username in Laravel 10.
Step 1: Install Laravel 10 To get started, you need to have Laravel 10 installed on your system. You can install it using Composer by running the following command in your terminal: Click Laravel site for other options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Install Composer Globally In Lammp Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/09/how-to-install-composer-lammp-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 09:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/09/how-to-install-composer-lammp-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Composer is an application-level dependency manager for the PHP programming language that provides a standard format for managing dependencies of PHP software and required libraries.
In this tutorials I will be showing you how to install Composer in Lammp in Ubuntu.
I will assume you have already install Lammp from it offical website Lammp offical site for details.
Steps to get started Open your terminal and input the code below install composer using the following command like so.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
