<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dipbits Technology Ltd</title>
    <link>https://dipbitstech.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dipbits Technology Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 09:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dipbitstech.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Upload Files TO Github Using Bash</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/18/upload-files-to-github-using-bash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 09:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/18/upload-files-to-github-using-bash/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bash is a Unix shell and command language written by Brian Fox for the GNU Project as a free software replacement for the Bourne shell.
A bash script is a series of commands written in a file. These are read and executed by the bash program. The program executes line by line.
Requirement You need to have a beginner knowledge on the following :
 Text editor for this tutorial we would using Visual Studio Code Terminal Git commands An account with Gihub  Procedure Open your terminal and navigate to the root directory of your project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Install Composer Globally In Lammp Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/09/how-to-install-composer-lammp-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 09:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/blog/2022/08/09/how-to-install-composer-lammp-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Composer is an application-level dependency manager for the PHP programming language that provides a standard format for managing dependencies of PHP software and required libraries.
In this tutorials I will be showing you how to install Composer in Lammp in Ubuntu.
I will assume you have already install Lammp from it offical website Lammp offical site for details.
Steps to get started Open your terminal and input the code below install composer using the following command like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://dipbitstech.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dipbitstech.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
